Khôi Tran

WEB DEVELOPER

tranvankhoi2002@gmail.com 788 929 2543 tranvankhoi.netlify.app linkedin.com/in/tranvankhoi github.com/koionaroll

PROFILE

Having grown up in the internet era, I have always had a personal interest in the ever-changing and innovative technology industry. My two years at SFU Engineering enabled me to understand the importance of practical skills over theoretical knowledge and led me to pursue a degree in web development. I hope to continue to nurture my interest in technology, build upon the programming skills, and am motivated to start a career in web development.

PROGRAM PROFICIENCY

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C++, React NodeJs, Express, MySQL, Agile Development, GitHub DOM API, User Authentication OAuth, Heroku, Jest, Styled Components, TypeScript, ViteJs

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma, Web Development

JAN 2023 - APR 2023 (Vancouver, BC)

Simon Fraser University | Sustainable Energy Engineering

SEPT 2020 - SEPT 2022 (Burnaby and Surrey, BC)

INTERESTS & SKILLS

Tech Enthusiast

- Operate a small-business refurbishing, building and reselling PCs
- Provide IT advice through volunteer program at retirement homes
- Freelance web development

Trilingual

- Fluent in English and French (oral and written communication)
- Fluent in Vietnamese (oral communication)

PROGRAMMING EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer | Magic Sim

APR 2023 (Vancouver, BC)

- Leveraged skills learned in bootcamp to create a passion project to share with the whole school and industry representatives
- Created an archival website to catalog and organize decks of collectible cards
- Tech stack include: ReactJs, ExpressJs, ScryfallAPI, SCSS

Front-End Web Developer | BrainStation x Visier Hackathon

FEB 2023 (Vancouver, BC)

- Was given 24 hours to solve the industry problem proposed by Visier: "How to make data analytics more accessible to new users"
- Prototyped a website that utilizes a chat box to guide the user on the information that they are seeing along with a way to toggle between a simplified / detailed view of the data

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

Ski Lift Operator | Grouse Mountain

OCT 2022 - FEB 2023 (North Vancouver, BC)

- Operated ski lift and ensured safety of riders
- Responsible for operating remote ski lifts
- Passed safety protocols for operating and working around ski lifts

Retail & Communications Associate | Pearson's Home Hardware

APR 2021 - APR 2022 (North Vancouver, BC)

- Responsible for cash register and log inventory
- Provided effective customer service
- Knowledgeable about hardware, construction and home improvement